我操
Fuck me.
我被这东西整惨了
I'm dying here.
我到另一边帮你搬一下
Let me get on the other side, work it from there.
一 二
One, two.
- 三 - 三
- Three. - Three.
妈的
Shit.
要搭把手吗
Need help?
好 数到三 操蛋的
Right. On three, motherfuckers.
一 二 三
One, two, three.
真为你们感到难为情
I'm embarrassed for you all.
嘿Herc 等我喘口气
Yo, Herc, I catch my breath,
我就把这鸟玩意儿的抽屉都打下来
I'm gonna shoot the drawers off this bitch.
它卡住了 副队
It's caught on something, Lieutenant.
到Carver那边去
Get over there with Carver.
一 二 你们知道怎么做
One, two, you know what to do.
他妈的怎么回事
What the fuck?
天 真被打败了
Jesus. My ass is kicked.
我一个人的时候还能挪动点
I could move it a bit when I was alone.
一定是莫名其妙地卡在门上了
It must've got wedged in the door somehow.
桌子是空的吧?
Desk is empty, right?
嗯
Yeah.
你检查过了吗?
You checked it?
这种速度 我们永远也搬不进去
At this rate, we're never gonna get it in.
啥?
What?
进去?
In?
进去
In.
难以置信 真他妈的难以置信
Unbelievable, unbe-fucking-lievable.
老天爷
Christ.
火线重案组 第一季 第四集 旧案
The Wire S01E04 Old Cases
* When you walk through the garden *
* You gotta watch your back *
* Well I beg your pardon *
* Walk the straight and narrow track *
* If you walk with Jesus *
* He's gonna save your soul *
* You gotta keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
* All the angels sing *
* About Jesus' mighty sword *
* And they'll shield you with their wings *
* And keep you close to the lord *
* Don't pay heed to temptation *
* For his hands are so cold *
* You gotta help me keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
"天堂和这儿一线之隔"  ——Bubbles
这案子对你来说太小儿科了
This case is a bit humble for you.
我知道案卷里没什么
I know it doesn't look like much on paper,
但你还是尽力而为吧
But see what you can do.
交上新朋友了?
Making new friends?
还没呢
Not yet.
我在少年法庭呆了一上午
I spent the morning down in juvenile court...
这些小鬼们知道街头小罪动不了他们...
But the kids know they can't be hurt with a street-weight charge...
所以没什么收获
So didn't get much there.
你试过了?
You tried?
被14岁的小鬼骂"滚开"  这滋味举世无双
Nothing like being told, "Fuck off," by a 14-year-old.
- 这个是我们最大的把握 - 他?
- Right here's our best shot. - Him?
他和Bubbles做了直接交易
Hand-to-hand with Bubbles,
犯罪记录多了去了
And he's carrying a long-ass sheet.
好了 谁先来? Dawkins女士?
All right. Who's first? Ms. Dawkins?
州院指控Marvin Browning 法官大人
State versus Marvin Browning, Your Honor.
一罪状为分发违禁物 即 海洛因
One count distribution of a controlled substance, to wit, heroin...
一罪状为分发违禁物 即 可卡因
And one count distribution of a controlled substance, to wit, cocaine.
数量?
Quantity?
一胶囊和一小瓶 法官大人
One gelcap and one vial, Your Honor.
保释建议?
Bail recommendation?
州院请求拘留被告 因为他涉及一项进行中的调查
State requests defendant be held, as he is part of a continuing investigation
此外 他因犯有前科 须强制劳教五年
And further, is subject to a mandatory five years without parole
不得保释
Because of prior convictions.
你想在这个案子里请求强制劳教五年吗
Will your office be seeking the mandatory five in this case?
正是 法官大人
Absolutely, Your Honor.
很好 我会考虑的
Very well, I'll take that into consideration.
至少引起他的注意了
Got his attention, at least.
中尉 来尝尝
Lieutenant, come have a taste.
来啊 我们在庆祝呢
Come on, we're celebrating.
Patrick去体检了
Patrick's going out on medical.
亲爱的可爱的第六节颈椎
Sweet, sweet Cervical 6.
我肩膀麻了 手臂麻了
My shoulder's numb, my arm's numb.
我的手指像是属于邻郡的某个狗娘养的
My fingers feel like they belong to some son of a bitch in the next county.
这是我跨出那狗屁警局的通行证
This is my ticket out of this rat-shit department.
66%即三分之二的养老金 我不用等30年工作期满啦
66 2/3 pension, and I don't have to wait for my 30.
我去也
I'm gone.
倒是他妈的帮了你的忙
Fucking yo did you a favor.
我得说 那小子下手重得像头骡
Kid hit like a mule, I've got to say.
你应该再缓几天
You should take a couple of days.
在打报告之前再好好想想
Think it over before you put in papers.
我姐夫在Moravia有家音像店
My brother-in-law's got a video store out on Moravia.
一星期有6000美元正经租金收入
Does $6,000 a week straight rentals,
8000美元黄片收入
Another $8,000 in porn.
他需要个合伙人
He needs a partner.
但那样会扣养老金
But they take that off the top of a medical pension.
如果作为收入上报当然会扣 他妈的我看上去有那么蠢吗
If you report it as income, they do. Do I look that fucking stupid?
祝您过得愉快 中尉
Have a nice life, Lieutenant.
你怎么了
What's with you?
你会想我吧 Augs?
You gonna miss me, Augs?
我他妈的怎么办 Paddy?
What the fuck am I going to do, Paddy?
这样吧
Tell you what.
我们一起 你觉得如何?
What do you say we go out together?
什么意思
What do you mean?
我是说 只是疼一会儿
I mean, it only hurts for a minute.
而且也不必发生在执行公务时
And it doesn't have to be line-of-duty either.
我是认真的 知道那些通往地下室的楼梯吧?
I'm serious. You know those stairs where they send us down to the basement?
- 嗯 - 那儿很黑
- Yeah. - It's dark down there.
你上个八九级台阶
You go up eight or nine steps,
放开扶手 跳上一跳...
Let go of the rail, take a little jump--
那样我会他妈的摔断脖子的
I'd break my fucking neck like that.
你不会摔断什么
You don't break nothing.
你在台阶上跳支小舞
You do a little dance on those steps,
和我一起享受三分之二养老金
You're up to two-thirds with me.
也许你还能起诉这座城市 再捞一点
And maybe you sue the city, get a little more.
不能说我们不配得到这些
Can't say we don't deserve it.
劳教五年 就为了一胶囊和一瓶子
Five in. For a one-and-one.
凭什么一份一加一就那么整我?
Now, why bang me like that for a one-and-one?
因为轮到你了 Browning先生
Because it's your turn, Mr. Browning.
出来混总是要还的
Everybody out there gets a turn.
你们都太小题大做了
You're all running wild here.
我想法官会明察秋毫 让你们收敛一点
I think a judge might want to take a look at this and slow you all down a mite.
这不一定 Marvin
I don't know, Marvin.
我看你的犯罪记录单...
I'm looking at your sheet here, and...
首先 叫犯罪记录单有点不大对
For one thing, it's a little wrong to be calling it a sheet.
更像本书
More like a book.
重要的是 我们让法庭卯上了你
Point is, we got the room to get a little crazy on you.
像她说的 轮到你了
Like she said, it's your turn.
给我们讲些故事
Tell us some stories,
可能就轮到别人了
It could be somebody else's turn.
故事
Stories.
Avon Barksdale
Avon Barksdale.
知道这个名字吗
Know the name?
所有高楼区操蛋的都知道这名字
Every motherfucker up in them towers knows the name.
我自己从没和他说过话
Myself, I ain't never really had a word with the man.
那Stringer Bell呢?
Stringer Bell, then?
Wee-Bey? Savino?
Stinkum? C.C.O.? Roc-Roc?
你要向我们透露谁的底 Marvin?
Who're you gonna give us, Marvin?
如果你不马上供出一个人 就离牢狱之灾不远了
You don't say a name soon, you're gonna be courtside.
好吧
All right.
什么好吧?
All right, what?
好吧 我坐牢去
All right, I'll take the years.
该死 小子
Damn, boy.
你该看看那警察
You should see the cop.
你先起床再说吧 把那个穿上
When you're ready to get up, put that on.
去A-7铺位报到
Report to bunk A-7.
A-7
A-7.
在早餐以前
Don't be later than breakfast.
还有谁在这儿?
Who else is up in here?
有西区的人吗?
Anybody from Westside?
大多是来自华盛顿的
D.C. boys, mostly.
华盛顿就在巴尔的摩市旁边
被收容者禁止跨越
他妈的漫漫长路
Long fucking drive.
我和你又被派去收集狗屁的线索
Me and you drawing another shit detail.
这不是狗屁的线索
This ain't a shit detail.
不是吗?
No?
我在他妈的Maryland州Marlboro的北部
I'm in Upper fucking Marlboro, Maryland,
还再往南走
And still going south.
看 又有一头牛
Look. Another cow.
发挥你的想象力 这个臭小子
Use your imagination. This little shitbird,
已经被我们海扁了一顿 他一见到我们
Having already been whipped good by us once he sees us, right?
就会像小贱人一样哭泣
And he starts crying like a little bitch
因为他知道我们大老远来Prince George郡 是为了继续整他 对吧?
Because he knows we drove all the way to Prince George's for more of his ass, right?
想想我们把他拎起来
Imagine we jack him up,
扔进一个小房间...
Toss him into a small room...
告诉他Mahone警探吃了他一拳差点挂掉
And tell him that Detective Mahone is near dead from the sucker punch.
可不是吗
No shit.
老酒鬼摔得晕过去了
The drunk old fuck suddenly slipped into a coma.
眼下局长和Mahone夫人在重症监护房 守在他床边
And now the Commissioner and Mrs. Mahone are at his bedside in the ICU.
我们奉命来到这里
And we've been ordered to come down here,
割下他的阴囊 放进罐子里 开车送回Baltimore
Rip off his scrotum, put it in a jar and drive it back to Baltimore,
和他妈的保龄球奖杯一起
So it can sit with the fucking bowling trophies
放在司法兄弟会分部的吧台后面
Behind the bar at the FOP Lodge.
FOP:由司法人员宣誓加入的一个兄弟会
好吧  然后...
All right? After which...
死小子停止啜泣...
Fucknuts stops whimpering long enough...
供出同伙 不管是谁
To just start giving people up, whoever.
Stringer Bell...Avon Barksdale
Stringer Bell. Avon Barksdale.
- 真的? - 那是
- Yeah? - Yeah.
小兔崽子背叛所有同伙
Little prick turns on everybody
我们给这案子打开了新局面
And we break the case wide open.
酷
Cool.
是吧?
Right?
"男孩村" 青少年服务管理收容所
那些参与直接交易的人 没有一个人交代?
So, from all them hand-to-hands, nobody flipped?
不 在城里那个地区  Barksdale比我们更有分量
No, that part of town, Barksdale carries more weight than we do.
就像这些见鬼的谋杀案
Just like all these fucking homicides.
证人说谎 证人受贿
Witnesses lying, witnesses paid off,
证人为捏造的故事作证
Witnesses backing up on their story.
这能怪他们吗
Can you blame them?
也不能
Not really.
平常我们只是走访路过那 而他们就住那在儿
Every now and then, we visit the projects. They live there.
你在调查Dee是吗?
Your man's Dee, right?
D'Angelo 是
D'Angelo, yeah.
这个案子里Dee是开枪的嫌犯
This one's got a Dee as a possible shooter.
和你的案子有关联
This one connects.
不会吧
No way.
这还有假? 我在调查这个
Yeah? I'm seeing it.
这是Diedre Kresson  Keeley的案子
It's Diedre Kresson, one of Keeley's cases.
得了吧Jay 这只是个女大学生
Come on, Jay, this is a college girl
在东北区的公寓厨房里被枪杀了
Blown up in the kitchen of an apartment up in Northeast.
这和西区剩下的那些混混有何关联?
How does this match with the rest of the Westside mopes?
他们没车吗?
They don't have cars?
没关联 Jay
This doesn't match, Jay.
有啊 看看这报告
It does. Take a look at your office report.
她被干掉的那个晚上 有目击者看到Dee和她在一起
A witness puts her with a Dee the night she's aced.
Jay 你觉得这里有几个Dee呢?
How many Dees do you think there are in the system, Jay?
不就一个街头诨名吗?
As a street name?
我问你Jimmy
Let me ask you something, Jimmy.
跟Barksdale有关的案子你有几件?
How many case files you got that you're putting on Barksdale?
也许12件
Maybe a dozen.
12件
A dozen cases.
那其中有几件是我们小队的?
So, how many of those are from our squad?
一件 Gerard Bogue
One. Gerard Bogue.
一件?
One case?
你们小队缺一个人都几个星期了Jimmy
Your squad's down a man for weeks, Jimmy.
我们替你们处理电话 跟进你们的案子...
We're gonna be humping your calls, catching your cases...
忙得像个转不停的陀螺 图个什么呢?
Hopping around like a one-legged pigtown whore on check day, and for what?
就为了让你搞大冒险  去破别人的案子?
So that you can have your big adventure and solve everybody else's cases?
这就是我听到的话吗?
Is this what I'm hearing?
他吃定你了 Jimmy
He's got you, Jimmy.
爱在哪里 McNulty?
Where's the love, McNulty?
- 他妈的给我点爱吧 - 好吧
- Show me some fucking love. - All right.
乖孩子 他是我儿子
Attaboy. He's my son.
你为什么不把这混混丢给Santangelo去查?
Why don't you just dump this loser on Santangelo?
再说 他本就该在这里帮我们忙
He's supposed to be down here helping us, anyway.
我不是找不到这混蛋吗?
I would if I could find the fucker.
一定接了别的活儿 影子都见不着
Must have another job, he's gone so much.
Daniels怎么说?
What does Daniels have to say about that?
没说 我给他打掩护呢
Nothing, I cover for him.
他昨天整天不知所踪 前天的大半天也是
He was out in the wind there all day yesterday, half the day before.
哥们 Keeley可真能磨洋工
Man, Keeley really dogged this one.
这里只有一份验尸报告
Ain't nothing in here but a 24
一些犯罪现场的照片和这个
And some crime scene photos, and this.
"Tywanda来电 没有进一步描述"
"Tywanda called. N.F.D.,
没有姓名 没有地址
No last name, no address.
"声称受害者在被杀前见过嫌犯Dee"
"Claims your victim killed after being visited by a suspect named Dee."
没有进一步描述
No further description.
但是有一个回电号码
There's a callback number, though.
那就回啊
So, call.
您拨打的电话无法接通
The number you have reached has been disconnected.
无法接通
Disconnected.
"他吃定你了 Jimmy"
"He got you, Jimmy."
好吧 操蛋的 他也吃定我了
All right, motherfucker, he got me, too.
那我打电话给Verizon(电信公司)看他们是否有新号码
So, I'm gonna call Verizon, see if they got a fresh listing.
现在开心了吧 贱人?
You happy now, bitch?
那个牌照你确定吗 Bubs?
You sure about that tag, Bubs?
我见过那辆货车
I seen the van.
打劫了大院 上了Amity街 朝Lexington去
It cleared the Court and rolled up Amity toward Lexington.
车牌被举报是从 停在这个街区的一辆车上被偷的
Plates were reported stolen off a car parked right here, on this block.
所以你觉得他们就在这附近?
So you're thinking they're from right around here?
也许吧
Maybe.
高楼区传言是Omar和他的人干的
Word in the Towers said it was Omar and his crew.
Omar? 他是谁?
Omar? Who's he?
你不认识Omar?
You ain't know Omar?
骇人者 Omar
Omar, the terror.
在这儿打家劫舍好多年
Been ripping and robbing out here for years now.
他厉害吗?
Is he fierce?
这家伙从来不儿戏
That nigger don't play.
姓什么?
Got a last name?
就Omar 他不需要姓
Just Omar. He don't need no last name.
他一伙的还有谁?
Who's his family?
你记得"无心"Anthony吗?
You remember No-Heart Anthony?
和他一起出道 他们是兄弟
Came up with him, they brothers.
"无心"Anthony?
No-Heart Anthony?
Kima小姐 别告诉我你不记得"无心"Anthony
Miss Kima, do not tell me you don't remember No-Heart Anthony.
该死 姑娘 你这么多年来是在哪儿当警察啊?
Damn, girl. What town you been policing at all these years?
现在我个人作为你的探子而感到羞耻
And right now, I am personally ashamed to be your snitch.
- 该死的 - 怎么?
- Shit. - What?
- 上课迟到了 - 上课?
- I'm late for my class. - Class?
- 12-14呼叫 - 12-14?
- 12-14. - 12-14?
请求联系我小队可以向13频道报告的人
Requesting anyone in my unit who's up to report to Channel 13.
35 我接手
35, I got that.
货出手了
Package be moving.
Avon的东西就是好
Avon's stuff always be good.
一次漂亮仗?
It's a sweet score?
还成
It's all right.
但过程出现了一点小状况
That play was a little bit raggedy in there, though.
我搞砸了 我知道
I fucked up, I know,
泄露了你的名字
Letting go your name.
我不介意你叫出了我的名字
I don't really care you shouted me out.
你难道没听说过吗? 公房区的人都知道Omar
Everybody in these projects been knowing Omar, you heard?
我只是不想他们来找你的麻烦 宝贝
I just don't want them coming down on you, baby-boy.
Shirley又来耍老把戏了
Shirley coming with her game.
他妈的每天都是这一套
Every fucking day with that shit.
Omar先生?
Mr. Omar?
我的支票来迟了
My check late.
嘿 Mike
Yo, Mike.
招待下姐姐
Hook a sister up, yo.
接下来干嘛?
So, what next, yo?
弄几把枪
Got some iron.
打算到东区打游击战...
Thinking about working the flush-and-run over on the Eastside...
等风声过了再说
Till things cool a mite.
行
That'll work.
你今晚不想在这里过夜吗?
So you don't want to lay over here tonight?
- 不 - 确定?
- No. - Sure?
不去 我要去看我妈
No, I'm gonna go see my mom.
保持联系
Keep it close.
知道了
I hear that.
谁是男子汉?
Who the man?
我得先去一个地方 然后我会送他回城
I gotta be somewhere first, but I'll run him back downtown after.
没问题 谢谢回复
No problem, thanks for answering.
- Bubbs - McNulty
- Bubbs. - McNulty.
怎么了?
What's up?
你听说过"无心"Anthony吗?
You ever heard of No-Heart Anthony?
谁 小Anthony?
Who, Anthony Little?
Argyle街1058号  公寓16-J室
1058 Argyle, Apartment 16-J.
他因为抢劫在Hagerstown蹲着呢 怎么了?
He's up in Hagerstown on a robbery bit. What about him?
好兄弟
My man.
去你们的
Fuck y'all.
知道那些狗娘养的白佬
You know how the cracker motherfuckers do
杀死一头鹿以后会怎么做吗?
When they kill a deer?
或者猎杀别的玩意儿时
Or, like, when they go out killing animals and whatnot?
把猎物绑在卡车的前面 四肢张开
Got them on the front of the truck tied up, stretched out,
让所有人都看到 对吧?
So everybody could see it?
懂我的意思吗?
You feel me?
我是认真的 这就是我想要的
I'm serious, that's what I want.
我要那操蛋的死给所有人看
I want that motherfucker on display.
我要杀鸡儆猴 警告院子里的人...
I'm gonna send a message to the courtyard about this motherfucker...
让他们知道我们可耍不起
So people know we ain't playing.
对 我们有弟兄正在查
Yeah, we got people on it.
告诉他们 找回钱给1000
You tell them it's $1,000 on the bucks...
干掉Omar 给2000
And it's $2,000 on Omar.
嗯 Bird在办
Yeah, Bird's on it.
还有Savino
Savino, too.
你瞧 Bird和Omar一起坐过牢 对吧?
You know, Bird jailed with Omar down the cut, right?
他说他是基佬
He said he all a faggot.
基佬? 不会吧
A faggot? Get the fuck out of here.
没错 说他在Jessup的牢里有一群兔爷
Yeah, said he had a whole stable of boys down in Jessup.
这个狗娘养的回来之后更不碰女人了
Tahis punk motherfucker got even less use for pussy now that he home.
看来他挺喜欢舔鸡巴的?
So, he gotta a lotta heart for a cocksucker?
嘿 我们来翻个倍玩如何?
Yo, we doubling down on Sweet Lips, all right?
做了他 他妈的给4000美元...
We make it motherfucking $4,000 on him...
如果在那之前 让我跟他打个照面 就给6000
$6,000 if I get the chance to holler at him before he get got.
就这样
Say no more.
把这些事办了
Take care of all that.
头晚货被抢
Stickup come up dead on the stash one night.
隔天条子就来扫荡
Police jumping out the next.
Pit那儿有情况?
Something up at the Pit?
也许吧
Maybe, yeah.
我外甥怎么样了?
What's up with my nephew?
不清楚 不错吧
I don't know. He doing good.
他倒是在那窝里做了不少生意...
He making that money out the hole, but...
但他可能有了自己也不知道的麻烦
He might have a problem he don't know about.
我罩着他呢
I'm on him.
嘿 你到底要带我去个仙境啊?
Yo, where in Leave it to Beaver-land are you taking me?
我有事迟到了
I'm late for something.
之后我会在回城的路上让你下车
I'll drop you after, on the way back downtown.
- 什么事迟到了? - 足球
- What you late for? - Soccer.
"吸"(音相近)什么?
Suck what?
射门!
Get in the goal!
传球 传球 好样的
Spread it out, spread it out, there you go.
第一队 集合!
First team, fall in!
爸!
Dad!
Mikey 你好吗?
Mikey, how are you?
嗯? 谁赢了?
Uh? Who's winning?
我们 4比1
They are, 4-1.
4比1? 谁帮你们进的球?
4-1? Who got the goal for you guys?
- Ricardo 我的助攻 - 助攻? 真有两下子
- Ricardo, my assist. - Assist? That's good.
中场休息要喝水 好吗
You've got to drink on the breaks, okay?
我可不想让你脱水
I don't want you to get dehydrated.
- 嗨 - 嘿
- Hi. - Hey.
这是Bubbles
This is Bubbles.
- 嗨 - 第二队!
- Hi. - Second team, come on!
- 去吧Mike 打败他们 - 再见 爸爸
- Go on, Mike, go get 'em. - Bye, Dad.
你迟到了
You're late.
他以为你这次也来不了了
He thought you weren't gonna come this time either.
这个工作 你知道这个工作的
This job, you know this job.
4:00他下学校巴士时我赶不过来
I can't get out here when he gets off the bus at 4:00.
两周一次的周末太少了 我要多看看他
I need more than every other weekend.
他需要我多陪陪他 Sean也是
He needs me more, so does Sean.
我不会让给你更多的周末
I'm not giving up any more weekends.
律师说平分是我...
50-50 split's all my lawyer says I have to give--
如果我整个星期都见不到他还算什么平分
It's not 50-50 if I don't see him all goddamn week.
- 你每天都能看到他... - 别凶我
- You see him every day-- - Don't curse at me.
- 律师说... - 去你的律师
- My lawyer says-- - Fuck your lawyer.
去你的
Fuck you.
刚才看到了吗?
Did you see?
嗯 看到了
Yeah, I saw.
去吧 你得上场了
Come on, you get out.
送到这里行了吗?
This good for you?
嗯
Mm-uhm.
天堂和这儿一线之隔
Thin line between heaven and here.
他怎么知道货藏在哪儿?
How did he know where the stash at?
缉毒的条子不知道 但他知道
The knockos don't know, but he do.
因为有黑鬼给他透风
Because some nigger's snitching.
哥们 不可能有人为Omar打探消息
Man, ain't nobody got to be snitching for Omar
他的手下也不可能 偷偷摸摸地来找藏毒的地方
Or his boys to creep by and see where the stash at.
靠 Bodie 看那小子的惨样
Damn, Bodie. Fucked that nigger up.
他被海扁了一顿
They stomped his ass.
为什么他打了缉毒条子还不去蹲大牢?
How he ain't courtside for banking a knocko?
小子 你怎么这么快就回来了?
Boy, how you get home so quick?
哥们 你偷了啥?
Nigger, what you steal?
Camry XLE(丰田的一款车) 你们想兜风吗?
Camry XLE. You all want a ride?
车就在拐角处
It's right around the corner.
哥们 男孩村不赖的
Man, Boy's Village ain't shit.
我只是太坏了 早不是什么叛逆小孩而已了
Ia'm just too bad for that off-brand little-boy bullshit, man.
那儿关不住我
It can't hold me.
你笑什么? 有什么好笑的?
What you laughing at? What's so funny?
换做是你 你还被关在那儿呢
If you was me, your ass would still be down there.
你见过市立监狱吗 小子?
You ever seen a city jail, nigger?
你杀过人吗?
You ever caught a body?
我是那个刚刚回来的人 记得吗?
I'm the one who just got home, remember?
一桩命案让我在Eager街监狱呆了八个多月
Eight months over on Eager Street with a body on me.
- 对 你有过一次 - 是啊 一件众所周知的而已
- Yeah, you got the one. - Yeah, the one you know about.
你们这些操蛋的该去打听打听
You little motherfuckers need to ask around.
嘿 在郊县那边
Yo, out near the county, right,
最东边那里
On the high end of the Eastside?
在那里有不少公寓 是吧
They got these apartments, out there, right?
以前住了个马子
So there was this little shorty who used to stay out there.
她长得....
She was, like....
我从没见过这么漂亮的女人
I ain't seen a female that fine since.
我得说 这马子很正
I gotta say, Shorty was right.
你上了她?
You fucked her?
没有 哥们 不是这样的
No, man, it wasn't like that.
她是和我舅舅一起鬼混的马子
This was a shorty my uncle was messing with.
有一段时间他们在一起...
They was going on at it for a little while...
后来她发现我舅舅还有一个马子
Till she find out that my uncle got another little shorty round the way.
更准确地说他有几个马子 明白我的意思吧?
More right to say he got a few of them around the way know what I'm saying?
于是 她发飙了 嚷嚷着要报警...
So, she goes off the hook, talking about calling the police...
举报一些她不该知道的事
About shit she ain't supposed to know.
我靠
Oh, shit.
可不是吗
Yeah, you know it.
但是瞧 那个时候我也有一腿
But see, I got some creep to me,
我叔叔知道这一点
And my uncle, he know that shit.
他们把我载到她的公寓
So they roll me out past her crib.
指给我看她就住在底楼
And they show me how she lives right on the ground floor,
一楼
First level.
我蹑手蹑脚地绕到后面 窗户旁
I go creeping around the back, to the back window.
我带着一把.45大枪
I got the .45 on me, the big gun.
我走到窗边 往里看 里面伸手不见五指
I walk up to the window and I look in, and it's dark as shit
因为是凌晨3点 啥都看不见
Because it's 3:00 a.m., and you can't see shit.
然后你干了什么?
What did you do?
于是我拔出枪...
So I pulled out the piece...
然后我开始用枪托轻敲窗户
And I start tapping with the back of it on the window.
敲得很轻
And it was quiet,
但又足以让她听见敲击声
But it was loud enough so she can hear that shit.
她就听到了这声音
That's what she heard, yo.
果然 她出来了
Sure enough, she comes out.
光着身子什么的
She's naked and shit.
我他妈的也搞不清楚
I don't know why the fuck,
她有件睡袍 她一边披上袍子
But she has a robe and as she slipping on her robe,
一边开灯...
She turns on the light...
她开了灯后
And when she does that,
屋里是亮的 她就看不见屋外的东西
And it's light on the inside she can't see shit on the outside.
靠 她赤条条的
Damn, she naked.
她听到窗户上有声音 她没办法...
She hears that shit on the window and she ain't got no choice...
只能走过去看是怎么回事
But to walk over there and see what it is.
她走上前...
She steps up...
往外看哪里跑出来的动静
Iooks out see where it's coming from.
然后呢?
What happened?
他开枪打死了她
He shot her.
嘿 Dee如果她真是那样的话
Yo, Dee, if she was all that,
你为什么不先操她?
Why didn't you fuck her first?
- 黑鬼 你真变态 快闭嘴吧 - 咋了?
- Nigger, you sick, just shut up. - What?
- 我只是说... - 这事不对头
- I'm just saying... - There is something seriously wrong.
这真荒谬
This is ridiculous.
就因为实验室冷藏机短路了...
Because a lab freezer goes out with an electrical short...
56起谋杀案的血液样本
Blood samples in 56 homicides...
和15起强奸案的...就让它变质了
15 rapes, are allowed to putrefy.
州检察官知道了吗?
State's attorney knows?
还有市长
The mayor, too.
我们很多鉴证室都使用了有25年了
Most of our trace lab is now 25 years old.
你们有试过筹款吗?非营利性质的?
You ever go outside for money? The non-profits?
比如?
Such as?
比如Abell基金会 我哥是一名董事
The Abell Foundation, for one. My brother's on the board.
如果你想让我帮你打个招呼....
If you want me to run it up there for you....
您能帮忙说说?
You could swing that?
问问无妨嘛 对吧?
Never hurts to ask, does it?
当然 法官大人
It never does, Your Honor.
既然我们想到一块去了...
So, in that same spirit...
Barksdale的案子调查得怎么样了?
Where are we with the Barksdale probe?
这是我造访的另一个原因
My other reason for stopping by.
探子深入虎穴 搜查和扣押
Hand-to-hands and search-and-seizures,
这些我听说过
I've heard about these.
正如你所见 一些二流毒贩落网
Some mid-level players caught up, as you can see.
瞧 虽然这不是毁灭性的一击
Look, it's not a knockout blow,
但是我们表现的态度鲜明
But we sent a clear message.
在上面 我看不到Barksdale的名字...
I don't see Barksdale's name anywhere...
还有Bell 也没有牵涉到谋杀案
Or Bell, or anything about the murders.
这次行动会带来些进展
The casework, it goes towards that.
不够
No.
那么 我们有活干了
So, we've got work to do,
对吧?
Don't we?
警察 该死地快开门!
Police, open the damn door!
该死地快开门!
Open the damn door!
什么?
What?
他妈地快开门!
Open the motherfucking door!
二楼前面没有情况
Upstairs front clear.
厨房没有情况
Kitchen's clear.
我在后门
I'm at the backdoor.
有人冲出去吗?
Anybody pop out here?
好了 安静
Okay, quiet.
二楼后面没有情况
Upstairs rear, clear.
他敢藏在这狗窝里
I'm gonna beat this bitch like a red-headed stepchild
我就剥了他的皮
For hiding up in this pisshole.
他妈的到处都是恶心的虫子
Goddamn creepy crawlers everywhere.
告诉Bodie 我们盯上他了
Tell Bodie we're on his ass.
很抱歉 我不该在门口爆粗口
I'm sorry for cursing at the door.
我是说 我不知道只有你在
I mean, I couldn't see that it was only you.
又是毒品的事吗?
Is it the drugs again?
想坐会儿吗?
Would you like to sit down?
我女儿死后
Preston came to me
我收养了Preston
When my daughter died.
当时他才四岁
He was four years old.
但即使这么小 我感到他很愤怒
But even then, I knew he was angry.
他母亲在外面讨生活
His mother lived out there,
吸上了
Caught up in it.
一段时间后
After a while,
她眼里就没有别的了
You couldn't make her see nothing else.
不 哥们 不是我们
No, man, that wasn't us.
凌晨2:30在高楼区? 你们可真疯狂 哥们
2:30 in the towers? You guys are crazy, man.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
你觉得你会如何面对呢?
So, how you think you gonna carry it?
对不起 夫人
I'm sorry, ma'am.
我为我们闯进来的方式感到抱歉
And I'm sorry for the way we came through here.
如果Preston路过...
If Preston comes past...
给他这个...
Give him this...
告诉他我们需要谈谈 行吗?
And tell him we need to talk, okay?
打扰了
I'm sorry.
你他妈的在里面干嘛?
What the fuck you doing in there?
谈话
Talking.
- 谈话? - 嗯
- Talking? - Yeah.
- 回见 - 行 再见
- See you later. - All right, catch you later.
我来开
I'm driving.
喂
Yeah?
McNulty
McNulty.
有个法官找你
Some judge for you.
喂
Yeah?
听着 我能再打给你吗
Look, can I call you back?
- 警长 能进来吗? - 嗯
- Major, sir? - Yeah.
我一直在想
I've been thinking.
尽管我知道这样做违法条例 但是...
It's a clear violation of the general orders, I know, but...
昨天晚上 我在家 光着屁股坐着
Last night, I'm at home, I'm sitting up buck naked.
一手握着一杯冰镇国产啤酒...
And I got one hand wrapped around a cold domestic beer...
一手握着我伟大的萎软的...
And the other wrapped around my magnificent, flaccid...
4.5英寸的命根子 竭尽全力...
Four-and-one-half inch wonder, and I am trying with all my might...
回忆在Hillendale泳池游泳派对上
To remember what Leila Kaufman's nipples looked like...
Leila Kaufman的上身泳衣滑下来时 她奶头的模样
When her bathing top slipped off at the Hillendale pool swim party.
- Leila Kaufman? - 是的 长官
- Leila Kaufman? - Yes, sir.
72年的夏天
Summer of '72.
可以说我意淫着这个风骚的婆娘...
I got this saucy wench in my gun-sights, so to speak...
我非常非常...
And I am dangerously...
接近高潮...
Close to engorged...
然后他妈的突然间他妈的不知从哪里...
When all of a fucking sudden, out of fucking nowhere...
冒出他妈的警探 他妈的Jimmy McNulty 跳进我的脑海里
Fucking Detective, fucking Jimmy McNulty pops into my head.
McNulty?
显然 我得睁开眼
Obviously, I gotta open my eyes
向自己承认 整个夜晚都被毁了
And admit to myself that my whole night is ruined.
结果 我百无聊赖...
At which point, I got nothing to do...
只能想着Jimmy McNulty的问题
But think about the problems of Jimmy McNulty.
因为显而易见 这家伙...
Because, clearly, this guy...
和他杀千刀的麻烦事 挡在我和尘世间所有的乐趣之间
And his fucking problems are standing between me and all worldly pleasure.
显而易见
Clearly.
首先 这不是他的错
First of all, it's not Jimmy's fault.
- 不是吗? - 不是
- No? - No.
Jimmy是个瘾君子 长官
Jimmy is an addict, sir.
他对什么上瘾?
What's he addicted to?
他自己
Himself.
这不好笑 长官
It's not funny, sir.
事实上 这他妈的就是个悲剧
As a matter of fact, it's a fucking tragedy is what it is.
这家伙 他以为自己
The guy, he has come to believe...
总是所有人里最聪明的混球
That he is always the smartest fuck in the room.
你知道吗?
And you know what?
这不是他的错 我们面对现实吧
It's not his fault, because let's face it...
他不会去Johns Hopkins大学  也不会加入门萨
He's not going to Johns Hopkins or joining Mensa...
Johns Hopkins大学：全美著名医科大学  门萨：高智商俱乐部
他只是他妈的在Baltimore警局打点小工
He's taking a fucking job with the Baltimore Police Department.
他头两年在凶杀科
His first two years in Homicide,
他和Tony Lamartino搭档 一起在Ulmansky的小队里
He's in Ulmansky's squad partnered with Tony Lamartino.
老天 好几个月里...
Christ, it must've been months even...
他的确是那些人中最聪明的混球
He was the smartest fuck in the fucking room.
你想说什么 Jay?
What's your point, Jay?
我想说的是...
My point is...
他管不住自己
He can't help it.
这使他很欠扁 我知道
It makes him an asshole, I know.
但这也使他成为一个好警察
But it's also what makes him good police.
去年 他给我破了8件案子
Last year, he gives me eight clearances.
有一件是腐烂的浮尸...
One of them was a decomp floater...
一连三星期身份不明
Who was John Doe for three weeks.
叫你的小子两周内搞定那个专案组
Tell your boy to wrap up that bullshit detail in two weeks.
他做到了 就可以回来 既往不咎
He does that, he comes home, clean slate.
你会喜欢的 Burrell坐在我对面
You would've loved it. Burrell is sitting across from me
拿着一叠街头逮捕记录 假装成竹在胸
With a handful ofstreet-level arrests pretending he has a plan.
那你怎么和他说的?
So, what did you tell him?
"不要班门弄斧 副局" 我他妈的这样和他说
"Never shit a shitter, Deputy. " That's what I fucking told him.
我干的不错吧 Jimmy?
I did good, right, Jimmy?
我得挂了
I gotta go.
"以Hicks的判决为例"
"Discuss the Hicks ruling as a manifestation
"讨论法官在现代法庭系统内"
"of the judiciary's attempt to maintain a speedy disposition
"尝试快速处理刑事案件"
"of criminal cases within a modern court system."
嘛东西?
What?
就是  "嘛东西?"
That's what I said. "What?"
Hicks判决是啥玩意?
What the hell's the Hicks ruling?
你刚刚是不是画了我的沙发?
Did you highlight my sofa?
什么? 没有
What? No.
你有
Yes, you did.
以前就在那儿了
That was there from before.
才怪 该死 Kima 记号笔洗不掉
Hell it was. Damn, Kima, marker does not come out.
不 我没画 我发誓
No, I didn't do it, I swear.
好 让我看看记号笔
Okay, let me see the marker.
你要我的记号笔 我得看看你的搜查令
You want my marker, I need to see a warrant.
我是认真的 你得有合理的根据
I'm serious, I need to see some probable cause.
我要打你屁屁 这个根据够合理吧?
I'm gonna beat your ass. How about that for probable cause?
给我记号笔
Give me the marker.
见鬼 真暴力
Damn, getting all violent and shit.
知道吗?你刚侵犯了我的人权
You know you just violated my civil rights?
没错 新规矩:不准在沙发上用记号笔
That's it, new rule: no marker on the couch.
你到那边的桌子上去做家庭作业
You get over to that table over there and do your homework.
去 拿上它过去
Go. Take it and go.
给我记号笔
Gimme my marker.
我要点苏打水
I'm gonna need some club soda.
该死 姑娘
Damn, girl,
这手机账单把工资都吃掉了
This cell phone bill must eat up the paycheck.
不会的 大多数是工作往来的电话 公司会报销
No, most of that's work, it's on the company.
Phelan不肯放手
Phelan won't let go.
我们有没有接近Barksdale?
Are we anywhere close on Barksdale?
没有 长官
No, sir.
那你要告诉我什么?
So, what are you telling me?
我没有什么要告诉您 长官
I'm not telling you anything, sir.
我等着您告诉我
I'm waiting for you to tell me.
这事儿你想我怎么做我就能怎么做
I can do whatever you need me to do with this.
如果你想我继续深入调查 我做得到
If you want me to push it further, I can do that.
如果你想就此罢休....
If you want it to go away....
如果你想调个别人来
If you wanna bring in someone else,
另外来一套查案的方法
Maybe do things differently.
你已将在找退路了吗 中尉?
You looking for the back door, Lieutenant?
这么早?
Already?
McNulty说这案子需要窃听
McNulty says this case needs a wire.
你认为他对吗?
You think he's right?
这案子是缺点什么
It needs something.
爬上那柱子吧 哥们
Just climb your ass up the pole, man.
不 哥们 这就行了
No, man. This'll work.
我才不要爬什么梯子
I'm not climbing no damn ladder.
你永远都打不中 哥们
You never gonna hit it, man.
砰!
Bomb!
房管局当我们傻子
Housing must think we just dumb.
是 是你的寻呼机还是我的?
Is that-- That's your pager or mine?
我的
That's me.
嘿 小心别砸到我的头
Yo, watch that shit on my head.
哥们 是从它妈的摄像头上弹下来的
Man, it ricocheted off the fucking camera.
得了吧 你需要些准头
Yeah, you need some aim.
喂 谁啊?
Yo, who this?
你怎么想?
So, what do you think?
窃听法案?
Title 3?
对 但不是为了搞窃听
Right, but it's not for a wiretap.
是去克隆呼机 我从Pearlman那儿拿来的
It's to clone a pager, I got it from Pearlman.
寻呼机?
Pagers?
侏罗纪时代的东西
Some kind of throwback thing.
你是说 为什么不用手机?
You mean, why not cell phones?
对啊 谁还用寻呼机啊?
Right. Who uses pagers anymore?
我和你说 昨晚我仔细地查看了一张手机账单
Tell you what, I was checking out a wireless bill last night.
所有的来电都有显示
Every incoming call was listed.
对极了
Right.
因此如果我们知道了Barksdale的寻呼机号码
So, if we get Barksdale's pager,
我们也许就不用停留在街头缉毒
we might get off the street.
也许还能追踪到供应商
Maybe even trace some supply.
"无心"Anthony是谁?
So, who's No-Heart Anthony?
"无心"先生在90年代初在家乡贩毒
No-Heart ran drugs in the homes in the early '90s.
几年前 不知怎的...
So, a couple years back, I don't know why...
他去了Randallstown 想打劫一家珠宝店
He finds himself in Randallstown, trying to take off a jewelry store.
他搞砸了 半个郡的人追他到市中心
He fucks it up, half the county chases him back downtown.
我猜"无心"先生琢磨着他逃不掉了...
And I guess No-Heart figures he's not up for doing the time...
因为他将一把.44手枪指 向自己的胸口 扣动了扳机
'cause he puts a .44 against his chest, pulls the trigger.
一把.44?
A .44?
造成接触性伤口
It's a contact wound.
两小时后在大学急救室里醒来
Wakes up two hours later in the University ER.
- 并且有了一个新绰号 - 正是
- With a new nickname. - Right.
Bubbles说前几天晚上是Anthony的兄弟
Bubbles says it's Anthony's brother who took off
卷走了Barksdale的货
With the Barksdale stash the other night.
那家伙叫Omar
Dude named Omar.
干这行可不容易 知道吧
It's not the easiest trade, you know,
抢劫毒贩子
Robbing dealers.
那样的人很可能携带武器
Man like that is likely to have a weapon on him.
我们抓住他 就可以按他一个罪名
We jack him up, there's a charge to work off.
如果他知道Barksdale的货在哪里...
And if he knows where the Barksdale stash is...
他很可能知道得更多
He probably knows a whole lot more.
看到了吧  又一个计划
See? Another plan.
问题是 我们还得说服别人
The thing is, we're gonna have to sell this.
你想向Daniels提议吗?
You wanna raise it with Daniels?
比起我 他更听得进你的话
He'll listen to you more than me.
Santangelo在哪儿?
Where's Santangelo?
他在物证科 今天有案子要上庭
He's at ECU. He's got a case going today.
迄今为止 我没有听到相反的声音...
As of today, I haven't heard anything to the contrary, so...
因此我们继续调查
We're gonna press on.
有什么好想法吗?
Ideas?
我们可以继续诱捕
We could continue with the busts.
但是我想这对我们深入调查没有什么帮助
But I don't think that's gonna get us too far off the street.
另一方面 上星期我们抓进来的人有寻呼机
On the other hand, the people we pulled in last week had pagers.
当McNulty抓D'Angelo Barksdale时 我们发现他也有
So did D'Angelo Barksdale when McNulty jacked him up.
我们可以克隆一些寻呼机 看看能得到什么信息
We could clone a couple of pagers, see where that takes us.
- 克隆什么? - 他们的寻呼机
- Clone what? - Their pagers.
他们被传呼 我们也被传呼
They get beeped, we get beeped.
我们看得到是谁打来的 什么号码
We see who's calling, from what number.
如果这样的话 他们为什么还用寻呼机呢?
If they're all that, why are they still using pagers?
为什么不多花些钱买个手机呢?
Why not un-ass a few dollars for cell phones?
这是行规
It's a discipline.
你窃听不了寻呼机
You can't bug a pager.
但你也不能用寻呼机打电话
But you can't make a call with a pager, either.
你会需要一台笔式记录器(一种电子设备)追踪所有平房区的投币电话
You're gonna want a pen register on all the payphones in the low-rises...
和其他跟寻呼机有往来的电话机
And any other phones that link to the pagers.
监控寻呼机需要什么?
What would it take to do the pagers?
窃听宣誓书
A wiretap affidavit.
我想我们从探子摸底到盯梢 已经有了足够的监控理由
I think we got enough PC from the hand-to-hands and surveillance.
我们几乎穷尽了一切办法
We got most of the exhaustion.
我听听都觉得累
I'm exhausted just listening to this shit.
很好
Good.
穷尽是使用电子拦截设备的法律要求
Exhaustion is a legal requirement for using electronic intercepts.
我们得证明别的办法都不起作用
We gotta prove nothing else works.
你看 我们做了突击检查
See, we did the raids,
做了街头逮捕 但没有人倒戈供认
We made the arrests, but nobody flipped.
我们没有线人能带着大家深入调查
We don't have an informant who takes us anywhere above the street.
真是没有办法了
That's pretty much exhaustion.
我们现在只要跟踪一个混混...
All we got left to do now is follow one of these mopes...
并证明我们跟不下去
And prove to ourselves we can't do it.
我们要向法官表明
We try to show a judge we can't make...
我们不能靠跟踪这些人破案 事实也的确如此
The case by following these guys, and we can't.
进了高楼区要怎么才能跟踪下去呢?
How can we keep on any of them when they're in those towers?
但你得表现出你努力过了
But you gotta show you tried.
我们有寻呼机的号码了吗?
Do we have a pager number?
这个写在货仓的墙上...
This was written on the stash house wall...
旁边写着"D"
With the letter "D" next to it.
是D'Angelo吗?
Is that D'Angelo?
你确认过了吗?
Did you check it?
就是他
It's him.
开工吧
Let's do this.
他要我们干什么?我不懂
What does he want us to do? I don't understand.
请我吃早饭 我就解释给你听
I'll explain it to you if you buy me breakfast.
你能再给我解释下
Will you explain to me again
为什么我要重现六个月前的犯罪现场吗?
Why I'm about to rework a six-month-old crime scene?
看看这杀千刀的档案
Look at this narrow-ass file.
Keeley啥都没做
Keeley didn't do shit on this.
- 但他记录了犯罪现场 - 到底是Keeley
- He did the scene, though. - This is Keeley we're talking about.
他妈的Jay和他的跳跃思维
Fucking Jay and his leaps of logic.
这案子跟我们现在查的毫不相关
This case is nowhere near anything we're doing.
那又怎么样?
So?
随便查查 让警督高兴高兴
Give it a shake or two anyhow. Make a sergeant happy.
随便了
Whatever.
你认识Lester Freamon吗?
Do you know Lester Freamon?
嗯 有点了解吧 怎么了?
Mm-uhm. A little. Why?
他和我们一起调查Barksdale案
He's with us on this Barksdale thing.
你好像说过他们都派累赘给你们
I thought you said they gave you humps.
他看着像累赘 表现得像累赘
He looks like a hump, he acts like a hump,
坐在那儿 玩弄着玩具家具
Sitting there, playing with his toy furniture.
Jimmy 他靠那玩意挣得比你工资还多
Jimmy, he makes more money off of that shit than you do off of this job.
别被Lester骗了
Don't let Lester fool you.
我已经被骗了 今天例会上 他露了一手
He did already.Today in roll call, he showed something.
嘿 他天生是个警察
Hey, he's natural police.
以前在凶杀科
He used to be Homicide.
- 为什么离开? - 问他去
- Why did he leave? - Ask him.
就是这间吗?
This is the one?
是 再没有租出去过
Yup. Hasn't been rented since.
操
Fuck.
他奶奶的
Motherfucker.
操 我操 操
Fucking fuck. Fuck.
操
Fuck.
身高: 5英尺3英寸(160cm)
操
Fuck.
Fuck
搞什么?
What the fuck?
操
Fuck.
- 不对 - 操
- No. - Fuck.
我操
Fuck it.
操
Fuck.
操它娘的
Motherfuck.
操
Fuck.
操 操
Fuck, fuck.
我操 操 操
Fuckity, fuck, fuck.
操
Fuck.
操 操 操
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
它奶奶的
Motherfucker.
妈的有了
Fucking A.
操
Fuck.
看
Check this.
狗娘养的
Motherfucker.
我操
Fuck me.
Sydnor步行 Carv开车...
Sydnor's on foot, Carv's in the car...
Herc 你去Amity后街的的天台
Herc, you need to be on top of the roof behind Amity.
怎么又轮到我做狗屁的活
Again, I get the shit detail?
我们的计划是跟踪D'Angelo
The plan is to stay on D'Angelo.
如果我们跟丢了 就跟丢了 懂吗?
If we lose him, we lose him, right?
我们会跟丢的
We're gonna lose him.
在高楼区跟踪不了
You can't follow people in the towers.
除非你有好借口 否则你不能在平房区逗留
You can't hang in the low-rises unless you got a reason.
我想确认一下 我们要跟丢他 对吗?
Just to make sure, we want to lose him, right?
跟丢他对我们有好处?
Losing him is good?
没错
Right.
那我们还跟踪个屁啊?
Then why the fuck do this?
好了 Herc 这次听我的 行不?
Come on, Herc. Roll with me on this one, all right?
那么 你其实还是个警察
So, you're police after all.
你知道你能做 但你一直不在做
You know what you doing, but you ain't been doing it.
你在缉脏科多久了?
How long you been in the Pawnshop unit?
13年又四个月
13 years and four months.
- 13年? - 又四个月
- 13 years? - And four months.
我得问一句...
I gotta ask you...
一个被派到缉脏科的警员到底干什么活?
What exactly does a police officer assigned to the Pawnshop unit do?
你从注册当铺收取所有
You intake reports from registered pawnshops...
价值50美元以上物品的报告
On all items valued over $50.
然后你给每件物品做索引卡
Then you make an index card for that item.
然后把索引卡归档
Then you file that index card.
如果有人想查 是否有失窃物品被当...
If someone wants to find out if something stolen was pawned...
我们就看是否有索引卡
We see if we have an index card.
如果有就有 没有就没有
If we do, we do, if we don't, we don't.
- 你就干这个干了13年? - 又四个月
- You did that for 13 years? - And four months.
你为什么申请调离凶杀科?
Why'd you ask out of Homicide?
我没申请
Wasn't no ask about it.
- 被炒了? - 嗯
- You got the boot? - uh-uhm.
你干了什么惹着他们了?
What'd you do to piss them off?
警务工作
Police work.
我想我得请你喝一杯
I think I need to buy you a drink.
就一杯?
Just one?
案子发生在87年的夏天 Brooklyn的一户人家里
Caught this case in a Brooklyn home in the summer of '87.
80岁的老太太
80-year-old woman,
在床上穿着睡衣被刺死
Stabbed up nightgown, in bed,
凶杀从后窗强行进入
Forced window, rear entry.
调查了好几周
Worked it for a couple of weeks.
查到了Curtis湾俩毛贼的名字
Got the names of two squirrels over in Curtis Bay.
毛贼一号招了 然后试图
Squirrel number one gives it up and tries
把所有责任都推到毛贼二号身上
To put all the weight on squirrel number two.
有证据支持供词吗?
Back up the statements?
二号在后窗上有指纹
Print it on the rear window for number two
一号在医药箱上有指纹
Another one for number one on the medicine chest.
那搞定了 对吧?
So, it's down, yeah?
更妙的是 毛贼一号供出了
Even better when squirrel number one drives it by the house
他们脱手老妇人钱财的地方
Where they fenced the old lady's shit:
收音机闹钟 电视机 烤箱
Clock-radio, TV, toaster oven.
那么问题出在哪儿?
So, what's the problem?
问题在于销赃的人
The problem is the fence.
结果是"美国新闻"里
Turned out he was the son of one of the big editors
一个大主编的儿子
Over at the News America.
这人负责午报...
This man is running the afternoon newspaper...
他儿子却是一塌糊涂
And his son is getting all fucked up
作奸犯科 在Locust Point嗑药
Doing the dirt and getting high down in Locust Point.
副局 我想他是想做个顺水人情...
The deputy, who I guess is in a favor-doing mood...
传话给警长...
Sends word down to the major...
叫我结案时别提销赃者
I'm supposed to make the case without the fence.
就提指纹证据和供词 就行了
Just the print hits and the statement. Play it like that.
他为什么要这么做
So he doing this for what?
想要收买一个卖报纸的吗
have some newspaper gay in his pocket?
嗯 我想是的
Yeah, I guess so.
是Burrell吗?
Is this Burrell?
不 不 是Mueller 在Burrell之前的副局
No, no, Mueller. Deputy Ops before Burrell.
那么 你怎么做?
So, what did you do?
你觉得我会怎么做?
What do you think I did?
我控告他销赃 还让他出庭作证
I charged him with receiving, then had his ass testify.
你本可以不提他就结案
You could've made the case without him.
就指纹和供词
Just on the prints and the statements.
嗯 可能是的
Probably, yup.
那为什么不这样做?
Why didn't you?
为什么?
Why?
你为什么作践自己追查Avon Barksdale?
Why are you fucking up yourself chasing Avon Barksdale?
审判结束一周后
A week after trial ends,
警长来问我想去哪个部门
Major comes to me asks me where I want to go.
我告诉他我不在乎 我喜欢跑外面 你懂吗?
I tell him, I don't care, I like to be outside, you know?
给我个他妈的巡逻的岗位 我仍旧能挣钱谋生...
Give me a goddamn foot-post I'll still make my money, you know...
把我调去Edmondson大道 我不在乎
Send my ass up to Edmondson Avenue, I don't give a shit.
你去巡街了?
You went to a foot-post?
警长回来问我不想去哪个部门
Major come back, asks me where I don't want to go.
他问得像是为了确定我能找到好归宿
And he asks it like he wanna make sure I land okay.
所以我告诉他 我他妈的不要和纸打交道
So, I tell him I don't want no fucking paper show.
不要该死的文职
No office shit.
只要把我他妈的派到外面 让我维护治安
Send my black ass outside and let me police somewhere.
结果去了缉脏科
Pawnshop unit.
真被整惨了
They got me good.
那他们为什么还放你出来?
So, why'd they let you out of the box?
为什么是现在?
Why now?
我想他们是把我忘了
I guess they just forgot about me.
靠 Lester
Shit, Lester.
你起死回生了?
You back from the dead?
你凤凰涅槃了
You rolled away the stone.
Bunk Moreland说你天生是个警察
Bunk Moreland says you're natural police.
千里挑一的好手
One of the few.
是啊 想当年呐
Yeah, I've had my moments.
警探...
Detective...
当他们问你想去哪个部门...
When they ask you where you wanna go...
他们会来问你想去哪个部门...
And they are gonna ask you where you wanna go...
替自己做件好事...
Do yourself a favor...
闭上你的嘴
Keep your mouth shut.
我去尿尿了 小伙子
I gotta take a tinkle, boy.
- 明白了 - 行
- I got it. - All right.
你好
Hello.
Kima在吗?
Is Kima there?
你是?
And you are?
告诉她是McNulty
Tell her it's McNulty.
找你的 Kima
For you, Kima,
一个显然喝高的白人小伙
A decidedly confused white boy.
天
God.
今天进展如何?
How'd it go today?
在221号就跟丢了
Lost him in the 221.
在平房区又找到了他
Picked him back up in the low-rises
天黑后在Schroeder街跟丢了他
And then lost him on Schroeder Street after dark.
干得好
Nicely done.
- 你还能开车吗? - 嗯 我没事
- Are you okay to drive? - Yeah, I'm fine.
我只是想谢谢你
I just wanted to thank you.
谢什么?
For what?
谢谢你今天在Daniels面前替我说话
For today, you know, with Daniels.
- 你该谢谢Lester - 我谢了
- You should be thanking Lester. - I did.
我只是也想谢谢你 Greggs警探
I just wanted to thank you, too, Detective Greggs.
不客气
No problem.
晚安
Good night.
已经很安了
That it is.
我错过了什么?
What'd I miss?
失恋?
Lovelorn?
更糟 孤独
Worse. Lonely.
你今天又没来上课
You didn't make it into class again today.
你说过你会坚持的
You said you'd stick with it.
我在努力呢
I'm trying.
现在事情很棘手
Things are hot right now.
我已经尽力了
I'm doing the best I can.
你自己说过你要做些别的事的
You said to yourself you need to do something else.
让我们俩更幸福的事
Something better for us.
- 你承诺过 - 哦 天
- You promised. - oh, god.
老天
Man.
我该拿你怎么办呢?
What am I gonna do with you?
你知道比你漂亮的女人 都为我的技巧神魂颠倒 对吧?
You know better women than you have fallen for my tricks, right?
衣服下面是什么?
What have you got under this?